[Music]
Sir, it's very important to understand how stress affects heart disease.
One thing we've added to this is that
when we sleep, our
mind relaxes, and when our mind relaxes, the
secretion of nutrients in our body slows down. This doesn't affect
our body's metabolism,
and
ultimately, our
food intake decreases. This means that the more stress we experience, the more
chemical changes occur in our body. The
most important factor,
or the hormone that
creates problems for many diseases, is
cortisol. When our stress
levels are high, the
levels in our body are very high, and this can lead to
anxiety,
increased heartbeat, and
metabolic changes. This can lead to
increased hunger,
obesity, or weight
gain, and we don't get to sleep.  Due to this back-
up hormone, our pancreas, from
where our insulin is secreted, is
perfect. If
our fortis level
remains high for a long time, then in the long term, these
people who
spill over further may develop diabetes.
Stress is a very
important factor, after that, the
development of diabetes leads to associated
diseases. Thirdly, due to stress or
cortisol levels,
many changes occur in our coronary arteries,
which may include inflammation,
draft formation, heart attack.
Overall, it is said that stress is a major cause of a
variety of diseases. Many
diseases arise due to stress
and it has been observed that heart problems are
a direct link among them.